# Malsor Ajvazi

## JUNIOR FRONTEND DEV

0038345638840 malsorajvazi@gmail.com github.io/malsorajvazi Prishtine, XK

I have extensive experience working with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I have a great eye for design, and I pride myself on being able to create clean, functional, and user-friendly websites. My expertise in web development also includes experience with frameworks such as Vue JS, and Node.js.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2023 - Present Junior Frontend Dev Freelance

2022 - 2023 Junior Frontend Dev at Beetroot Academy **2020 - 2022**Wordpress Developer
Hosting management

#### **EDUCATION**

Junior Frontend Dev at Beetroot Academy, Prishtina 10000 B.A. Computer Science University of Bussines & Technology, 2019 - Ongoing

#### **AWARDS**

2023 Junior Frontend Dev Certification at Beetroot Academy

#### **SKILLS**

Languages: English, Albanian HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT Vue JS, Git & Github Node JS Adobe Photoshop Host management

### References

Available upon request